pornjam.com 2003-10-18

# Privacy Statement

**IndianCDstore.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ IndianCDstore.com ](http://12.206.13.226/cdstore)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.  

####  Cookies 

Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart, and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user.  Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.  Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates.  For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site.  If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers).  However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

####  Advertisers 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

####  Registration Forms 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address). 

Contact information from the registration forms is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

####  Order Forms 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). 

Contact information from the order forms is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. 

Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications for registration, and to bill the user for products and services. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **IndianCDstore.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

####  Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number ), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry \- SSL.  For security reason, We don't store user credit card information in our website instead we ask user to enter it every time they order CDs and DVDs.  While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘surfing’.  To learn more about SSL, follow this link <http://home.netscape.com/eng/ssl3/>    

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line.  All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices.  Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.  Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk.  When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information.  Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices.  Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected.  Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [support@indiancdstore.com ](mailto:support@indiancdstore.com)

####  Choice/Opt-Out 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us . 

  1. You can send email to [ support@indiancdstore.com ](mailto:support@indiancdstore.com)

####  Data Quality/Access 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can send email to [ support@indiancdstore.com ](mailto:support@indiancdstore.com)

####  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   

* * *

Generated by [Privacy Wizard](http://privacy.bcentral.com/)
